Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alumni Relations office, 1884-1989; RG0014 Series 12; 36.5 Linear feet (Box 8, Box 26)
  - GWLA calendars of events, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - GWLA newsletters, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Alumni relations misc. corresp., 1974-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - GWLA nominating comm. reports, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 02/10/1982 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 09/15/1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 05/02/1985 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 06/18/1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - GWLA exec. comm. mtgs. reports, 09/09/1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - GWLA annual board mtgs. minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - GWLA annual board mtg. minutes, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 08/11/1965 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 08/10/1966 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/14/1975 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 01/27/1976 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/26/1977 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/11/1977 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/25/1978 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/17/1978 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/23/1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/10/1979 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/22/1980 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/21/1980 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/12/1981 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/13/1981 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - GWLA board of directors, 05/20/1982 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 10/08/1982 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/26/1983 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - GWLA board of directors, 10/29/1983 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 02/02/1984 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/24/1984 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 02/29/1984 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/17/1984 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 05/16/1985 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - GWLA board of directors mtg., 11/16/1985 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - G.W. alumni directory, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - G.W. alumni directory, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - G.W. alumni directory, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - G.W. alumni directory, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - G.W. law alumni directory, 1866-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - G.W. law alumni directory, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - G.W. law alumni directory, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - GWLA chapter Alabama, 1974-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GWLA chapter Alaska, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - GWLA chapter Arizona, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - GWLA chapter Arkansas, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - GWLA chapter California, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - GWLA chapter Capitol Hill, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - GWLA chapter Capitol Hill, 1967-1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - GWLA chapter Capitol Hill, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - GWLA chapter Colorado, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - GWLA chapter Connecticut, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - GWLA chapter District of Columbia, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - GWLA chapter District of Columbia, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - GWLA chapter District of Columbia, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - GWLA chapter Delaware, 1967-1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - GWLA chapter Florida, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - GWLA chapter Georgia, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - GWLA chapter Georgia, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - GWLA chapter Hawaii, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - GWLA chapter Hawaii, 1974-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - GWLA chapter Idaho, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - GWLA chapter Ilinois, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - GWLA chapter Illinois, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - GWLA chapter Indiana, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - GWLA chapter Iowa, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - GWLA chapter Kansas, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - GWLA chapter Kentucky, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - GWLA chapter Louisiana, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - GWLA chapter Maine, 1975-1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - GWLA chapter Maryland, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - GWLA chapter Maryland, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - GWLA chapter Maryland, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - GWLA chapter Massachusetts, 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - GWLA chapter Arkansas, 1975-1983 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - GWLA chapter Michigan, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - GWLA chapter Minnesota, 1967-1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GWLA chapter Missisippi, 1975-1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - GWLA chapter Missouri, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - GWLA chapter Montana, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - GWLA chapter Nebraska, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GWLA chapter New Hampshire, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - GWLA chapter Nevada, 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - GWLA chapter Nevada, 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - GWLA chapter New Jersey, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - GWLA chapter New Mexico, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - GWLA chapter New York, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - GWLA chapter New York, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - GWLA chapter North Carolina, 1975-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - GWLA chapter Ohio, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - GWLA chapter Oklahoma, 1975-1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - GWLA chapter Oregon, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - GWLA chapter Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - GWLA chapter Pennsylvania, 1970-1982 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - GWLA chapter Rhode Island, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - GWLA chapter South Carolina, 1975-1985 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - GWLA chapter South Dakota, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - GWLA chapter Tennessee, 1975-1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - GWLA chapter Texas, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - GWLA chapter Utah, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - GWLA chapter Vermont, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - GWLA chapter Virginia, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - GWLA chapter Virginia, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - GWLA chapter Virginia, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - GWLA chapter Washington, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - GWLA chapter West Virginia, 1976-1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - GWLA chapter Wisconsin, 1969-1982 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - GWLA chapter Wyoming, 1971-1982 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Black law students association (BALSA), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - International alumni, 1969-1981 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Foreign students & alumni assn., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - ABA midyear meeting, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - ABA midyear meeting, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - ABA midyear meeting, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Fed bar assn., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Fed bar assn, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Fed bar assn, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Fed bar assn, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - DC bar, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - GW commencement, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - GW commencement, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Official files - orig. const., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Pres. Elliott trips to west coast, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - NLC council advisory council, 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - GW law alumni directory, 1866-1952 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - GW law alumni directory, 1865-1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - GW law alumni directory, 1865-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - GW law alumni directory, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - GW law review, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - GW bulletin, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - GW bulletin, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - GW bulletin, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - G.W. Law Bulletin, 1998-2016; RG0014 Series 12 (Box 26, Folder 1-8)
  - First annual mid-year meeting of GWLA, 03/25/1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The NLC library, 03/19/1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - NLC student directory 1983 & 1985, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NLC commencement: 5/22/77, 5/18/80, 5/23/82, 5/7/89, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - GW convocation: 10/12/65, 2/18/80, 2/16/81, 2/15/82, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - A university in the nation's capital 1821-1947, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The GWU in the nation's capital, 10/01/1955 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The GWLA scrap book Nov. 1, 1941, 04/1934-11/1941 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The supreme court of va., 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Supreme court of Va., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - GW NLC graduates, 09/1977 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Commencement, 05/23/1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Va. swearing-in ceremony, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - February 1980 law graduates, 02/1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 05/24/1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 05/23/1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 05/22/1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 05/20/1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 05/19/1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - GWU convocation, 02/17/1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - GWU convocation, 02/21/1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - GWU convocation Feb. 20,1978 and Feb. 19, 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - GWU convocation, 02/15/1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - GWU convocation, 02/21/1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - GWU convocation, 02/20/1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - GWU convocation, 02/17/1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - History of the law school, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Commemorative booklets
  - Law alumni directory, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Law alumni directory, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - GWU commission yr 2000 report, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Journal of international law and economics editorial alumni list, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - General services, information, 03/1970-08/1972 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Expansion of law center, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Equal justice foundation, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Estate planning, 05/1972-03/1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Enrichment activities, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Deferred giving, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Dimock gallery, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Data mail, inc., undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Directory correspondence, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Assoc. Dean Schwartz, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Dean Kramer's retirement luncheon, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Dean's discretionary fund, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Dean Barron reception, 11/10/1982 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Danzansky dedication, 11/01/1984 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Developing/ revitalizing chapters, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - College and university press, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Colonial women booster club, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Case - council for advancement and support of education, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Historical data law alumni, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Law school relations committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - The Adventures of Captain Kidd & the Counterpart - manuscript, 06/23/1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Jacob Burns party, 04/29/1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Jacob Burns law library, 11/1968-08/1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Dedication of Jacob Burns library, 10/18/1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Burns Van Vleck Moot Court Award, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Banners, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Achievement awards - general alumni, 1965-1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - AALS/sect. on institutional advancement, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Association of American Law Schools, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Alumni, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Alumni directory, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - GWU annual report, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Letters of recommendation, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Long range planning committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Marvin Center facility, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Marvin Center activities, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Memorial gift file, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Military law committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - National Law Center for Innovation in Corrections (GWU), undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Law school faculty, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - National Law School general corr., undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Nominating committee, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Nominating committee, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Nominating committee, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Northwood Institute, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Order of the Coif, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - ODK (Omicron Delta Kappa), undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Notices, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Notices, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Notices, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Notices, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - New office, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Partners in large law firms, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Placement, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Placement office materials and corr., undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Referral information, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Reunion weekend, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Requests for alumni class directory (correspondence), undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Reunion weekend, 04/23/1982-04/25/1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Past presidents award, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Placement, 1969-1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Postage, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Postal information, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - SGBA alumni correspondence, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Smith Center, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Robert H. Terrell - law school, 1970-1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Alumni college, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Army and Navy Club, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Honorcraft, Inc., undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Interamerican Bar Association, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Law of the Land, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mailing information, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dean's special funds, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Old letterhead, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - NLC advisory council, 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - NLC advisory council, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Black Law Students Association, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - ABA Breakfast New York, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - California, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - California, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - California, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - California, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - California, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - California, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Colorado, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Colorado, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - D.C. chapter, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - D.C. chapter, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - D.C. chapter, 07/1974-12/1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - D.C. chapter (local), 1967-06/1974 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - D.C. chapter (local), 1967-06/1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - D.C. chapter law assn., undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - D.C. chapter law assn., undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - D.C. chapter law assn., undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Florida, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Florida, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Florida, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Florida, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Florida, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Florida, 1976-1972 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - GWLA - California, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - GWLA - California, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - GWLA - California, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - GWLA - Colorado, 1971-1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - GWLA - Colorado, 1971-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - GWLA - D.C., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - GWLA - Florida, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - GWLA - New York, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - GWLA - New York, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - GWLA - New York, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - GWLA - New York rosters, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - GWLA - Virginia, 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - GWLA - Virginia, 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - GWLA - Founders Day comm., 1967 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Night school issue (Dean Barron), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - GW alumni law faculties, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - GWLA professional achievement through 1987, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - GWLA fund - Herrick Letter, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Harold & Violett George Fund, 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - John F. Ellis mem. fund, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Judge Justin Egarton fund, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Robert M. Cooper - prof. emeritus, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Manuel F. Cohen lecture, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Elizabeth Freret fund, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Belva Lockwood fund, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Smoot memorial, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - NLC finding support, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit A, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit B, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit C, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit D, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit E, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit F, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit G, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit H, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - GW Law Ctr Exhibit I, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Dulles fund advisory committee, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - GWLA exec. comm. corresp., 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Revised GWLA constitution, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - NLC Finding Support, 1970-1979 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Idaho state bar assn, 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Idaho state bar assn, 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Idaho state bar assn, 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Military law cmte of D.C. bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Military law cmte of D.C. bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Military law cmte of D.C. bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Federal bar assn, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Federal bar assn, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Constitution amended as of Oct. 3, 1969, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - 105th anniv. celebration Oct. 23, 1970, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 105th anniv. celebration Oct 23, 1970, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 105th anniv. celebration Oct. 23, 1970, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General alumni governing board, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - General alumni governing board, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - General alumni governing board, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - General alumni governing board, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Airlie foundation general file, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - General alumni governing board, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - General correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - General correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - President Elliott general alumni trips, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - CAD J.D. file, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Law library, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Law library plaques, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Friends of the law school, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Dean's representatives, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Dean's report, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Minutes advisory council, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Placement, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - GW law assn centennial banquet, 10/22/1966 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Foreign law students assn., 1983 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - NLC student bar assn., 1973-1985 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - NLC student yearbook, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Sesquicentennial year celebration, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - GWLA itinerary, 1971-1982 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - ABA annual meeting Atlanta, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - ABA annual meeting San Francisco, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - ABA annual meeting Dallas, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - ABA annual meeting New York, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - GWLA California, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - GWLA California, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - GWLA Colorado, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - GWLA D.C., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - GWLA D.C., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - GWLA D.C., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - GWLA Florida, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - GWLA Florida, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - GWLA New York, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - GWLA New York, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - GWLA Texas, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - GWLA Texas, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - GWLA Texas, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - GWLA Washington, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Julia Jennings, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NLC law library plans, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1979 reunion, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1978 50th reunion, 05/05/1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1927 50th reunion, 05/06/1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1927 50th reunion, 05/06/1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1975 7th reunion, 03/18/1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Columbian University annual, 1901 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The National, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Stare Decisis yearbook, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Yearbook of National University
  - The Docket, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Yearbook of National University. Please note that within RG0123 the records of National University contains the Docket from 1922-1942.
  - The Docket, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Docket, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Res Gestae, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Yearbook of GW law school
  - Stare Decisis, 1912 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - G.W. law association bulletins, 1915-1943 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    1915-1925, 1930-1932, 1936-1937, 1941, 1943